export const ScienceData = [ 
    {
        id:0,
        question:`Who was the first African American to successfully perform open heart surgery? `,
        options: [`Ben Carson`, `Charles Drew `, `James McCune Smith`, ` Daniel Hale Williams`],
        answer: `Daniel Hale Williams`
    },
    {
        id:1,
        question:`He was a scientist and loved to study plants. He developed over 300 ways to use peanuts!  `,
        options: [`George Washington`, `George Washington Carver`, `Lonnie G. Johnson`, ` George Jefferson`],
        answer: `George Washington Carver`
    },
    {
        id:2,
        question:`Like a good water gun battle? You can thank this NASA engineer for inventing the Super Soaker.   `,
        options: [`Lonnie G. Johnson `, `Otis Boykin`, `James E. Easton`, ` Michael Jackson`],
        answer: `Lonnie G. Johnson `
    },
    {
        id:3,
        question:`Thomas L. Jennings was the first African-American to receive a patent. It was for _____.  
        `,
        options: [`a cotton spinner`, `a dry-cleaning process`, `a printing machine`, ` the typewriter`],
        answer: `a dry-cleaning process`
    },
    {
        id:4,
        question:`First African American woman to be a millionaire selling hair products. She created a cream to help hair grow back.  `,
        options: [` Madam C J Walker`, `Madam D J Walker`, `Harriet Tubman`, ` Jennifer Freeman`],
        answer: ` Madam C J Walker`
    },
    {
        id:5,
        question:`Garrett Morgan invented the ___________________ to make sure firemen are safe from harmful gas `,
        options: [` Gas Tank`, `Gas Mask`, `Gas Pump`, `Gas`],
        answer: `Gas Mask`
    },
    {
        id:6,
        question:`___________ was the first African American Woman to go to space in 1992. `,
        options: [`Mae Jemison`, `James Madison`, `Katherine Johnson `, `Mae Davis`],
        answer: `Mae Jemison`
    },
    {
        id:7,
        question:`__________________ invented the clock in 1753. `,
        options: [`Benjamin Banneker`, `Benjamin Button`, `Albert Einstein`, ` George Washington`],
        answer: `Benjamin Banneker`
    },
    {
        id:8,
        question:`Dr. Charles Drew thought of and organized the _________________. It saves millions of lives.  `,
        options: [`Blood Bank`, `Flu shots`, `Cell phone`, ` Polo Vaccine`],
        answer: `Blood Bank`
    },
    {
        id:9,
        question:`He invented the ultraviolet camera `,
        options: [` George Carruthers`, `Garrett Morgan`, `Booker T. Washington`, `  Andrew Jackson`],
        answer: ` George Carruthers`
    },
]
